export default {
  "trivia_questions_data": [
    {
      "question": "The Bible is...",
      "choices": [
         "Written by Adam and Eve",
         "The word of man ",
         "Just another book",
         "The inspired word of God"
      ],
      "answer": "The inspired word of God"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the two major parts of the Bible called?",
      "choices": [
         "Old Testament & The new creation",
         "The New Testament & The Old Testament",
         "The Moses Story & the Jesus story ",
         "There is only one part of the bible  "
      ],
      "answer": "The New Testament & The Old Testament"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is God?",
      "choices": [
        "A Spirit",
        "The Creator",
        "Our Father in Jesus Christ",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did Jesus save us from?",
      "choices": [
         "A bad headache",
         "The consequences of our sin, spiritual death",
         "Never being sad",
         "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "The consequences of our sin, spiritual death"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does God reveal to us who He is?",
      "choices": [
        "Through creation",
        "Through the Bible",
        "Through our conscience",
        "Through Jesus Christ",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Jesus?",
      "choices": [
         "The Son of God, and our Savior",
         "A liar ",
         "A trickster ",
         "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "The Son of God, and our Savior"
    },
    {
      "question": "We are saved:",
      "choices": [
         "By our intelligence ",
         "By the prayers of our parents and Church",
         "By the songs we sing",
         "By the good things we do for other people",
         "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "None of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is prayer?",
      "choices": [
         "Saying words you don’t mean.",
         "Talking to yourself.",
         "When you open up your hearts and speak with God.",
         "Speaking for other people to hear what your saying."
      ],
      "answer": "When you open up your hearts and speak with God."
    },
    {
      "question": "Who should our prayers be directed to?",
      "choices": [
         "Our friends ",
         "Our parents ",
         "Our heavenly Father",
         "Ourselves"
      ],
      "answer": "Our heavenly Father"
    },
    {
      "question": "When Jesus taught, 'when we pray we should go into our private room, close the door and pray.' What did he mean?",
      "choices": [
         "God doesn’t like open spaces",
         "If we can’t find a private room we shouldn’t pray",
         "Our focus should be on God, without distractions",
         "God can only be found in private rooms"
      ],
      "answer": "Our focus should be on God, without distractions"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the best definition of Repentance?",
      "choices": [
         "Feeling sad",
         "Turning away from our sins and coming back to God",
         "Telling people about all the bad things we did",
         "Never saying sorry"
      ],
      "answer": "Turning away from our sins and coming back to God"
    }
  ]
}
